americarx.com 2009-05-19

# AmericaRx.com : Your Privacy respected. SSL secured, confidential data storage and committed to protect your personal information.

| | | SHOP BY CATEGORY   
---|---  
|   
---  
---  
|   
---  
---  
---  
---  
---  
|   
|   
  
| 

**Information We Collect**  
We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect on our site to provide you with a superior shopping experience. And also to Inform you about products, services, and promotions whenever we feel it is neccessary. We always respect your Privacy and time.  
  
---  
  
**  
Your Account Details**  
When you place an order, we will ask you to set up "your account and Log-in Info," which includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date, as well as certain other information. Using your account information, we will only contact you in case we are not able to process your order or we have a problem with any of your information. We will not sell your information to anybody. You can always acess your account by log-in in our site and modify the information about you at any time you want.  
  
We only share your shipping information with third parties working on our behalf to complete your order, such as UPS, USPS and FedEx.  
  
**Security**  
Appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures are there in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet, We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database that is away from our Web site database so it isn't connected to the Internet, to keep it safe from hackers.  
  
**  
America Rx.com** uses secure servers to protect all your personal information. Our checkout process uses industry-standard SSL encryption to ensure the privacy and security of your information.   
  
**  
Commitment to Privacy**  
Your privacy and credit card security is utmost important to us. The personal information we collect includes shipping and billing name and address, email address, phone number and credit card information. This information is used only to complete your order. We do not share your personal information with outside parties for marketing or for any other purpose. However, we do email our customers from time to time with news and special discounts offers, but you always have the option to permanently remove your name from our email list.   
  
However If you direct, we will release prescription or other customer information to your authorized representative, the prescribing or other authorized practitioner caring for you, or such other person as you may direct. At the direction of the patient and to the extent specifically authorized by law, we will release such information to other persons, including Third Parties and insurance plans.  
  
**Third-Party Sharing Information** **  
Fetch Back**  
We work with Fetch Back to display Retargeted ads to our site prospects, on our behalf, across the Internet. They collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during in this process. To read FetchBack’s Privacy policy, [clickhere](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html). If you do not want FetchBack to collect this information, you may opt out of their service. Opting out will not in any way effect your use of our site. To Opt-Out, of FetchBack Retargeting, please [clickhere](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html). Visit the Network Advertising Initiatives Opt-Out by [clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  

From time to time, we may partner with certain companies who, in conjunction with their membership programs or rewards programs, require that we disclose purchasing information about their members who visit our Web store (for example, to earn points for purchases made on our site through links from the partner site). We will disclose only the information required to make these programs work for you and support your membership in them. In addition, we disclose this information to such companies only if you have consented first, including consent implied by your agreement to the membership or participation rules. If you do not want us to disclose that information to the strategic partner, then you must contact the partner directly.  
  
**  
Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM)**  
Your privacy is very important to us.WE assure you that, in accordance with our Privacy Policy, **America Rx.com**, will not distribute our customer list to third parties.   
  
**  
Your Comments**  
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to drop us an e-mail at sales@americarx.com.  

Thank You for visiting this page and wish you Happy Shopping Experience. You can always reach us by using our Toll-Free Help.  
  
* If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, and how we use it.  

|
